Hey,
why did you bring me to a place like this?
Don't be so impatient.
Go check the private room on the right.
You mean here?
Chief,
it's been so long.
Did you miss me?
Did you call me here
just to say this?
Oh,
don't be so cold.
So this is the type
he likes.
Who's there?
Girl,
why is she here?
And she's with that boy
from Yungong Pavilion.
Chief, you...
Girl,
what are you doing here?
Chief,
who is this girl?
You haven't introduced us yet.
Just passing by.
Sorry to interrupt your fun, Mr. Yan.
Please continue.
I was actually foolish enough
to think he liked me.
This girl brought another man
to the restaurant
and didn't even explain herself.
Let go. You're hurting me.
Come back with me.
No, let me go.
Let me go.
I can walk by myself.
Don't pull me.
Let's go.
I'm afraid you can't leave.
Hmph,
long time no see.
By order of the High Priest,
you must die here.
Hei Wuya,
you joined the Demonic Cult?
Hmph, cut the crap.
Brothers, attack!
Kill!
Don't worry.
I'll protect you this time.
He actually didn't just stand by
and watch this time.
Didn't they say he was seriously injured?
Damn it.
Ah!
Stop!
Let's
go after them.
Ah!
What's
wrong?
Don't scare me.
Madam, Senior Medical Maniac is not here.
I heard you became his apprentice
a long time ago.
We can only rely on you now.
I'll figure something out.
Oh,
why are you calling her Madam?
Does she deserve it?
Besides, I think
the Chief is like this
all because of her.
It's you.
Who exactly are you?
Stop making false accusations.
You really are a wild girl,
not even recognizing me.
I am Feng Qingwu,
one of the Ten Halls of Yanmen.
A piece of trash like you
who only brings disaster to the Chief
dares to call herself Madam?
I didn't call myself Madam.
So noisy.
Is this how you care for a patient?
Sect Leader, you're awake.
Let me help you.
No need. Feng,
take her out.
Ah, Sect Leader, don't be so heartless.
Why won't you turn around?
Where did your bravado go?
My dear wife.